I will give you 5 to 6 tips for getting the best health insurance
in this video, keeping these in mind you
can get the best health insurance for yourself, okay, that is, if you
already have any disease or if you
want to get complete health insurance for your family because there is also Aunty Health
Insurance, okay,
you can cover yourself as well as your children,
okay,
or if you want to get health insurance for your parents, if
they already have any disease, then
you will take care of these things so that you can
subscribe, keep in mind that I will
talk about health insurance here, I will
not talk about license,
what happens, whether it is yours or
someone else's, they get
scattered a lot in liking and subscribing, if you
go for treatment of these cancers, then your
one Surja becomes 60 to 68,000 lakh rupees, so no
matter how much setting you have, it will go into it, so that is why it is
said
friends, health is wealth, okay, so you
People should mix their money in the right way
and should also know how to manage their health in the right way, only then the
money you are
saving and investing will be useful,
you will be able to save it,
otherwise if any family member
gets any disease then all the money goes down the drain
and the basic is fine, then you people should keep 5 to 6
tips in mind so that you can
buy your child everywhere, but I will not take the name of any company here
that you
go and buy it from this particular company, rest of the health
insurance, you people know
what it is, how it works, you
people know the minister premium, quarterly, Chhath
Mai's salute, you all know
that the premium has to be decided, if you
people are buying songs
then let's do something, you are watching
all these channels and I am here, if you all once
again welcome you to our and your daily report channel, if you are
new to the channel and
want to keep more things like this then support this channel
also and
connect yourself with the upcoming videos, subscribe
and click on the bell icon so that you can get notified about the
upcoming videos  I can get notifications of videos
and one more request from you guys is that
you guys should share this video with others as well,
okay because at this time
people will buy more health insurance due to corona virus,
okay so they should know some tips
so that they
can make the best buy for themselves, so the first tip for
you guys is that you should
talk as soon as possible, otherwise the more you
delay in buying health insurance, the more
premium you will have to pay, okay, that means if
you guys are between 25 or 30 years of age from the middle of your family,
okay then what will happen in this is
that you guys will get
a good cover on the premium, that means
friends, for the health insurance of 10 lakhs,
here for whatever disease
you are going to cover,
you will have to pay a higher premium,
okay so that you guys want to take cover for
a particular disease, let's say cancer,
and you want to take cover for this disease, if it is
40-50 years old, then the insurance company does
not even cover it in history, okay so what
happens if  Deti Divya
demands a higher premium from you
because the average age of you people is
considered to be 6, this is the age of the Indian team,
okay now if it is a lid then
what happens with this is that people know
that now school na
Ajay particular as your age increases the more your
premium will decrease, if you like it as soon as possible then
you will get a
lower premium,
secondly you should listen to your playlist,
okay, like what does it
mean, that is you can read it, your
insurance will be closed, now
here if you want that you
go till this year then there you will have to that house,
now that will be closed in which you
people have taken two cups of sugar here,
if it is not there then what will you have to do, you will have to do it
again and as I
told you earlier that the more you go ahead
in this thing, the more premium you will have to pay,
then the same health insurance which is
covering you and your family will have to be available
at a higher premium,
so this is a very important thing and
this is the second important thing  You should
look at the reliability that
comes with Lifestyle University, you
can remove it for life time, okay, you
people get 750, after a good number of years the insurance becomes
lighter, then also you
can remove it, okay, so buy such a health
insurance, the next thing
you have to keep in mind is that if you people get
hospitalized or anyone gets
hospitalized, whichever applicant is there,
whoever has taken health insurance, then keep in
mind what kind of expenses are
added in it, read the documents very carefully
and from whichever app you are taking it, especially
notice this particular point and talk to them, complain about the
room rent, which are extra expenses,
if you people live somewhere then your
electricity bills are also taken, okay, so are
all those things being covered or not and are they being
covered 200% or not
and what are those things which are not being covered in it,
okay, so that your
extra expenses are covered  There are expenses that should
not be borne by your pocket. Now suppose you are
used to living in good facilities, now here because of that health
insurance you can
shift to the general ward. Okay, if your
health insurance
also covers your room rent or if it
also covers expenses, then you can go for the same
or you
can get your own particular liquid. If you do
not have a subscription here, then you have a problem there. If you do not have a
subscription, then
friends, you should not look at the third thing, do
not look at the room rent, look at the small expenses.
Written, you should see that after
how many days are your previous illnesses being
covered? The insurance
policy will cover you. Okay,
like you subscribe, subscribe and share
and what is the subscription, that is, by doing our subscription you
subscribe and if there is
any problem with the subscription and the next
question is that will that insurance policy
cover me the deposit because whatever is there from hut,
when will it be covered after one year, after six months?
When will the discussion happen together? Okay, so
according to your requirement, if you want to
get the cover, then you have to pay
more here, but the
security of money will be more for you and the
money that you have for it, you have to keep it aside, it will be
nutritious for me and my children, so
you should keep in mind that whatever
diseases you have already, if there is
any disease going on in the family, then
when will it actually be covered in the future, okay, this is a
very important point which you people have to keep in
mind, plus you have to tell others about this too
because people do
not pay much attention to this and the other thing
you have to keep in mind is that you people should see
how much coverage you people are getting, okay, up to
how much coverage can Mercury provide in your illness,
you people may have to pay a premium according to 5 lakhs, 10 lakhs,
but you people will have to
confirm that if this is my device in reality, then
how much cover can I get,
how much coverage can I get, so
You should keep this in mind while buying insurance
and note down all these things that
I have told you in 2.1 and
ask your insurance provider and if you have already
taken health insurance then immediately
call the insurance provider and ask how much of these things I am getting
and how are I getting it and at
least I am getting it that I would like to
send you this so that you can see whether
you can add your family members in future or
not, okay by chance it may be
that you have you, your wife, your
daughter or son and later
after two to three years another one
comes in your life, okay then now he/she will also
need insurance, okay so now for that you should
add a particular person in the same family in your health insurance policy, okay what will happen with this is that
you will have clear
flexibility in payment plus the remaining
premium will be quite useful, so you should keep these things in
mind that if your family is
complete then there is no problem, it does not matter
much but if you
They have knowledge and you guys are newly
married, you have health insurance, you have less bike, then
you guys should always keep in mind that you can
add a family member in future
that I am fine, then you should keep all the things in
mind, one more thing you should keep in
mind is that you should buy the right policy,
whatever I have told you,
you should keep those things in mind,
you should keep this size checklist in your mind about that policy, because there are many
apps which look more at their profit,
look more at any problem in which they are
getting more commission
and they get more commission in that,
but you people get less benefit,
and what your insurance policy
company does is that in which users get less benefit, they
give more commission to those apps in them, so that
agents send more to them
and they get more commission, I am
not talking about all the apps, but still there are
some apps which look more amazing,
if you people  If we talk about ourselves then
you should keep these things in mind that if
you are an agent then don't feel bad, these
things happen everywhere, somewhere or the other the
world comes, so you should share this video as much as possible
and from this
they also get to know
what things to take care of and if you like this video then
definitely like it and
support me on the channel and to see for yourself
subscribe to the channel and like it, you will get
notifications of the videos, so see us,
you can go to sex